//問題文を格納する要素です
const quiz = [
    {
      question: "_____ the captain has turned off the fasten seatbelts sign, passengers are free to move about the captain.",
      answers: ["Once", "However", "Already", "In addition to"],
      correct: "Once"
    },
    {
      question: "Ms.Chou _____ that the missing document was simply put into the wrong file folder.",
      answers: ["concerns", "suspects", "remits", "provokes"],
      correct: "suspects"
    },
    {
      question: "Ms.Kumasan's ability to work well under pressure made a _____ impression on haer supervisors.",
      answers: ["favorable", "favor" ,"favorite", "favors"],
      correct: "favorable"
    },
    {
      question: "Since the office manager left on maternity leave, her two assistants have _____ most of her responsibilities.",
      answers: ["been handled", "handle", "to be handled", "been handling"],
      correct: "been handling"
    },
    {
      question: "If customers are _____ dissatisfied with our products, they may return the merchandise to us for a full refund.",
      answers: ["any", "when", "ever", "since"],
      correct: "ever"
    },
    {
      question: "The new laptop computer is _____ of processing information at twice the speed of the previous version.",
      answers: ["enable", "possible", "capable", "available"],
      correct: "capable"
    },
    {
      question: "The committee has made a selection, but it is subject to _____ by management.",
      answers: ["approving", "approve", "approved", "approval"],
      correct: "approval"
    },
    {
      question: "You may keep the sample as a gift _____ you decide not to make a purchase.",
      answers: ["or", "even if", "but", "as though"],
      correct: "even if"
    },
    {
      question: "The _____ students spend studying and preparing, the more likely they are to score highly on the exam.",
      answers: ["long", "longer", "longest", "length"],
      correct: "longer"
    },
    {
      question: "When the driver gets to the office tower, he should go _____ the building and turn into the employee parking lot, where the client will be waiting outside.",
      answers: ["past", "about", "over", "after"],
      correct: "past"
    },
    {
      question: "The founder of the company _____ a speech at the upcoming banquet, just prior to the presentation of awards.",
      answers: ["had made", "making", "has made", "is to make"],
      correct: "is to make"
    },
    {
      question: "Ms.Ackerman has visited the Madrid branch so often that she feels _____ she were already working there.",
      answers: ["about", "when", "that", "as if"],
      correct: "as if"
    },
    {
      question: "The International Peace Conference _____ as planned on Saturday.",
      answers: ["concluded", "held", "achieved", "invited"],
      correct: "concluded"
    },
    {
      question: "All the passengers in this aircraft are required to wear seat belts _____ on board.",
      answers: ["despite", "while", "during", "and"],
      correct: "while"
    },
    {
      question: "An investigative report _____ last year alleges that a local brokerage firm had intentionally misled investors.",
      answers: ["published", "is publishing", "was published", "publishes"],
      correct: "published"
    }
  ];
